Okay, we're going to talk about a new blog post.
And this blog is going to talk about
what any client receives
when working with Wolfpack.
And it's not only about technical
tools and processes that I bring in.
But also about a data quality and AI
safety mentality and
the knowledge about what AI. AI is capable of,
is not capable of, what AI can do and cannot
do, and how to dive
deeply into how the Technical
aspects of any organization work to first find
all the places where you want to restrict AI,
just as you would a new employee. And that whole
discovery process happens without an
AI model talking to the system,
and we, for example,
map out all the services. Connections and the ports,
and make sure that we design AI guardrails that only allow
AI visibility to certain ports,
and explicit guardrails that both restrict
and Audit those other ports to make sure that
the AI never infers access to those.
Another example would be how AI chatbots
are allowed to respond to customer incoming.
My SOP for that is that they
are not allowed to send messages,
period. At the inception of the system,
the agents are only allowed to draft responses that a human must
ultimately send. And so the guardrail we would set up there is
to create an agent. Layer on
the AI chatbot,
so it doesn't have the tool to send a message in its
arsenal, and it cannot access that tool in the MCP
of the email provider. For an
AI chatbot to get around that restriction would require a
lot of human prompting and human interference.
Other guardrails could be set up in the form of.
Of auditing agents, which need to be seen
as anonymous check bots,
not finger-pointing blame machines,
because those auditing bots will be.
Looking at communication across the whole company and can find vulnerabilities
and can also find opportunities for things like great customer
service in a follow-up or an upsell or.
drawing connections between different vendors
or customers that a human being wouldn't have the
bandwidth to ever make.
And so let's talk about the technology that I bring into a
client right away. First,
on the internal Wolfpack side,
the client is given their own security.
Processing environment with their own client
ID, which anonymizes their name in the Wolfpack system.
This is my own system that has been in place for
15 years. Years and keeps all client work in
their own gated community.
The AI that I use internally for my clients is also gated
in a similar way, where AI sessions in one client.
Folder have absolutely no visibility into any other client
data. And this is a similar approach
to having a client ID in
a data warehouse. Where client data is
never allowed to commingle.
This is set up from the beginning for all clients,
and this is a fully tested system for the last year.
Um the other thing that this client will get is their own.
Secure subdomain of the of the Wolfpack web
where we can host deliverables in a password-protected
hosted environment. This makes for amazingly easy collaboration
on proposals, SOWs,
SOPs, and
delivering links and Sharing research all
can be done in a convenient
hosted way. Another thing the client
gets is the BQL
command line product, which creates their
own BigQuery analytics environment for them.
They own all the data on their
side with Google's protection.
And that's how they
retain, the client retains. All ownership of raw data and has a full
audit trail. And setting that up is
a simple five to ten minute process that can be
done from the command line. And
that also gives them a looker environment where
I can immediately start prototyping tables
and charts and workflows and dashboards.
All within, and the only requirement is that the client have or set
up a Google workspace with at least
one or two, ideally, two users.
And the reason. For two Google Workspace users,
is one is going to become your AI agent's own identity.
That's about $8 a month as of today for that user.
And a big part of my approach is with
the Google's built-in permissions,
you can lean on them and trust those permissions from restricting AI's
access to to certain
things across your Google workspace, such as Google Drive,
Google Docs, certain shared drives,
shared folders. If you create pipelines
where that AI user Is
restricted from those things, then you can sleep easy that they're not reading them.
And this goes also for platforms like Notion or Trello or
your Salesforce or whatever. If you create Accounts
using that AI account and restrict them just as you would a low-level
employee to read-only access and only on certain roles where
they can see certain data or interact with certain teams,
then you're not relying on. Instructions and prompts that you've set up internally,
but on the platform's own ironclad permission
structure to safeguard your AI's interference with things that you
have not given it permission to interfere with.
And then, with that big query environment,
the expected cost for a client with for a small or medium-sized
business client is going to be about $100 a month because
that is basically The lowest level
of storage you can buy for Google
Cloud storage. Cloud,
you need to fact-check that because it might be even lower,
but I don't want to understate. Costs for new clients,
but you know that I can set up the client
for almost the cost of that workspace user,
$8 a month, they can get set up,
but really. Realistically, they're going to incur some compute charges and some storage
charges. And I put that in the $50 to $100
range from what the research is showing me now.
On top of that, the client is going to want. At least a pro-Cloud
subscription for the highly subsidized processing rates.
So they can use the skills and products that I,
AI products that I send them and get a good deal on the usage.
I think just one of those pro accounts should.
Suffice unless they're a development-heavy firm in which
they're going to use Macs, and they probably already haven't.
My system also uses Codex as an independent code reviewer,
but a Macs subscription. Over there is not required because
the code reviews don't generally take anywhere near the amount of usage
you'd need to justify another pro account there.
And then the other thing that the client gets installed.
um is the the uh Wolfpack AI Command
product, which is the tying together of Notion with GitHub
on a a Python agent layer,
um, that ties the business together and gives AI
visibility into all silos,
and can the AI can become a bespoke project manager
and development developer's best friend.
Let's see, I think that
about covers what the new client gets.
I also want to mention A
section at the end of the blog which is kind of what to expect
when working with Ryan.
And one of the things is Transparent
communication using Notion and
project management of our statement of work,
completely. Transparently with the client,
weekly meetings that are 30
minutes or sometimes a little longer if discussing deliverables or
new statements of work. The
statements of work will also be hosted on the Wolfpack web in
the client's own sub-domain,
where we can always go back to that or make amendments that are visible
to both teams. You'll
get secure file sharing link that's run
through Google Cloud Storage.
And I'll also I'm fine to work
with client-provided FTP.
I'm very delivery-focused,
and I am not afraid to. To come to the client with questions
to refine deliverables along the way.
It is my style to work very autonomously,
but I'm very detail-oriented, so I will always ask.
Questions before making assumptions in order to improve the quality of the deliverable.
The other thing they can expect with me are Loom videos explaining
questions, debugging, or Giving a tour
of a deliverable. I love using Loom.
They also get access to me as an AI coach if they want me
to bring AI tools, advice,
and And best practices to other members of their team in
parallel to the statement of work.
They also get self-tested and Self-audited
deliverables where I have
adversarial agents judge and test the work in order
to make it of a higher quality and make sure I've thought of.
Different scenarios and weaknesses
The client will also get One
or several repositories based on the structure of the work.
These will be either yeah,
these will be just private repositories.
That are shared with the clients so their development side can audit
as they want to.
Oh, yeah, an ROI calculator is part of every statement
of work as well. That I,
together with the client, figure out how ROI
is going to be measured on my project. In dollars,
you know, and I need to measure that monthly
and always have that in mind that the work I'm doing informs the
ROI on that exact path. Examples of ROI.
ROI can be followers gained,
but then we want to monetize, you know,
dollars per follower so I can justify my fee
and show ROI on it. A lot of times conversion
is a goal of a project. And so we would calculate for
every basis point of a conversion
increased company wide,
what is the dollar amount outcome multiplied
against A O V by using A O V to dollarize every
zero point one of a percent increase in conversion is equal to X number
of dollars in Revenue.
And ideally, I like to look at two numbers for my ROI.
One is revenue-based ROI, and the other is profit-based ROI.
I don't like to look at one or the other because generally,
the The profit ROI is very non-linear and difficult
to nail down.
After direct and indirect expenses are backed out of the revenue
number, you can come to 10 different conclusions.
Conclusions about a profit ROI. So,
I like to look at a profit ROI constrained within
some assumptions,
and then also a gross revenue ROI that we'll just track over time.
And then The client can look at both and compare against what they're paying
Wolfpack and see that it's had a return for their company.
In general, if I can't figure out how to compute ROI with the work
I'll be doing, I am hesitant to take.
The project until there's a more direct link between
my fee and the client's return.
Otherwise, it's not a win-win.
I should talk about what's in my wheelhouse and what's not.
What is in my wheelhouse is analytics
heavy work and insights heavy work,
where I I'm working with normalizing
raw data into an analytics,
a queryable analytics layer,
and then running statistics on that and producing data visualizations.
and doing ad hoc projects to connect
past data points with marketing initiatives,
pricing initiatives, content initiatives,
and also on the operations side. with going to vendors
and asking about cost reduction based on trending SKUs in the
data or trending categories in order to direct
our internal sales team or purchasing team To
focus their time, prioritize their time on the brands and parts
of the supply chain that have the most return or the most volume.
I'm great in a situation where we're tying together many data sources.
That don't speak the same language or look the same,
such as marketing impressions and clicks and cost
with e-commerce data, which is fulfillment and pricing
and taxes. as well as customer service data
like returns and time per ticket closed,
things like that. Since I've been an operator for most of my career
in leadership, I Can't help but think how all of that
works together. And so I find myself at a place in my career
where my best place is not in any of those verticals,
it's in all of them. And so I think what I'm
not. Great at, I don't have any enterprise experience.
I've had enterprise clients, but I've never been in an internal enterprise
as an employee. So I don't pretend to know how projects
are bought and how I. Data and insights are disseminated
across those organizations. I've only been adjacent to them.
I'm also not in advertising and I'm not in
the CMO's group. I just tend away from marketing.
The beginning of my career was all marketing,
and it wasn't for me.
I prefer the product side a lot,
and it's more natural to me, and my work is more absorbed on the
product side. Other
place of weakness is I haven't worked in
clean energy or the energy sector.
I haven't worked in education.
You know, so I just don't know those industries.
I have worked in consumer packaged goods and in
subscription-based software as a service.
I've worked in entertainment a little. I've had clients like HBCU.
And Time Warner when working in my early career,
so we're exposed to the mechanics of those communication
verticals. Okay,
I think that's plenty of a transcript. For Claude to give an
outline for this blog. And Claude,
I want you to make an outline and
break it up into sections in the order that you think it would be.
Best digested in this blog post.
And then I want you to write the blog post
according to that outline, but use as much original
copy from this transcript as you can.
While just removing ums and erms and pauses and noises
I make, but keep as much of the actual copy
in my voice and If
it's grammatically incorrect for this first version you're making,
I don't care. I want you to keep full sentences
and phrasing from this transcript as much as you
can for the first version.
So, what I'm expecting is the outcome is a lot of this transcript
verbatim, but in a different order.
Okay? And then the third thing you're going to do is judge
that draft. As a
potential client hiring Wolfpack,
and show me where I
should put more support. What I should consider
cutting, and where I should change
my wording according to your advice.
But I don't want you to then rewrite it. Want the three things: the
outline in the order you think should work.
Number two, written draft,
number three, feedback on that draft.